[
  {
    "question": "I ____ apples so much.",
    "answers": ["love", "like", "hate"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The color of grass is ____.",
    "answers": ["green", "light green", "dark green"]
  },
  {
    "question": "We get honey from a ____.",
    "answers": ["bee"]
  },
  {
    "question": "There are  ____  planet in the Universe.",
    "answers": ["8", "Eight"]
  },
  {
    "question": "We use our eyes to ____.",
    "answers": ["see", "look", "watch"]
  },
  {
    "question": "We live in on planet called ____.",
    "answers": ["earth"]
  },
  {
    "question": "We use a blanket when it is ____.",
    "answers": ["cold","winter"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Something we use to clean our hands is ____.",
    "answers": ["soap", "handwash", "sanitizer","water"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Birds use their ____ to fly.",
    "answers": ["wings", "feathers","feather","wing"]
  },
  {
    "question":"I can ____ a big Elephant",
    "answers":["see","watch"]
  }
]
